~Thanks for watching on Crunchyroll.com~
やっと来てくれたか。
You finally came.
What is the situation?
状況は？
敵は おそらく 50はいる。
I'd say there are about fifty
of the enemy.
Compared to that,
there are just four of us left alive.
それに比べ こっちの生き残りは
オレたち４人だけだ。
It'll all be over soon.
We will all attack at once.
もう少しで ケリがつく。
一気にいくぞ！
皆さん このクナイを 一斉に
敵側へ投げつけてください。
Everyone, please direct these kunai knives
towards the enemy all at once.
あとは 私一人でやります。
I will do the rest...
そんなムチャな！
いくらなんでも。
That's crazy! Not even you could...
Shut up and do as he says.
黙って 言うとおりにしろ。
これから 木ノ葉の黄色い閃光の
戦いが見られるぜ。
We're about to see
the Yellow Flash of the Leaf in battle.
一瞬だ。 見逃すなよ。
It'll happen in a flash. Don't miss it.
It's healing well...
((だいぶ よくなってる。
But don't over-exert yourself
or you'll open up the wound.
(でも あんまりムリすると
傷口 開いちゃうよ))
((オレや お前が傷ついたとき➡
When you and I were wounded,
Rin saved our lives with
her Medical Ninjutsu!
リンは いつも 医療忍術で
命を救ってくれたんだぞ！
アイツがいなけりゃ オレもお前も
とっくに死んでたんだぞ！
If she hadn't been there,
we'd both be dead by now!
(今は 任務のことより
リンを助けるほうが優先だ！))
Right now, saving Rin takes priority
over the mission!
((確かに ルールや掟は大切だが➡
Kakashi, rules and regulations
are indeed important.
それだけが すべてじゃないよ。
But that isn't everything.
Didn't I teach you...?
教えたろ。 状況に応じて➡
There are times
when the situation requires
(臨機応変に対処しなきゃ
ならないときもある))
impromptu responses
against the enemy.
I believe that the White Fang
was a true hero...
((オレは 白い牙を
本当の英雄だと思ってる。
確かに 忍の世界で➡
Sure in the world of ninja,
ルールや掟を破るヤツは
クズ呼ばわりされる。
those who break the rules and regulations
are regarded as scum...
But...
(けどな 仲間を大切にしないヤツは
それ以上のクズだ))
those who abandon their comrades
are worse than scum!
Kakashi Chronicles
~ A Boy's Life on the Battlefield ~ Part 2
《見つけたぞ。
I found them...
落ち着け！
オレにだって できる！》
Calm down... I can do this!
I'll take care of it.
(タイセキ)オレが 片付けてくる。
その間に お前は 幻術を続けて
さっさと 情報を聞き出しておけ。
In the meantime, use your genjutsu
and get the information from her.
迷彩隠れの術。
Camouflage Jutsu...
All right... Here I go!
よし いくぞ！
Go where?
どこへだ？
K-Kakashi... How come you're...?!
カ カカシ… お前 どうして!?
ま お前みたいな泣き虫忍者１人に
任せておけないでしょ。
Well, I can't leave this up to
a crybaby ninja like you, can I?
カカシ…。
Kakashi...
白銀の髪に
その白光のチャクラ刀…。
That silver-white hair and
White Chakra Blade...!
まさか お前…
木ノ葉の白い牙!?
Don't tell me you're...
the "White Fang" of the Leaf?!
これは 父の形見だ。
This is my father's keepsake.
((忍に必要なのは
任務に役立つ道具だ。
To carry out his mission,
useful tools are essential to a ninja.
(感情なんてのは
余計なものなんだよ))
Something like emotions are useless.
《カカシ お前…》
Kakashi...you...
なるほどな。 白い牙のガキか。
I see... You're the White Fang's kid...
なら ビビる必要はねえな。
Then there's no need to
be afraid of you.
《やっぱりな…》
I thought so.
匂いは 完全に消されてる。
The scent has been completely erased.
かすかな空気の流れや 物音で
敵の位置を判断するしかないぞ。
We'll have to locate him
by the slightest movement
and noise he makes.
ど… どこだ？
Wh-Where is he?
Obito, behind you!
オビト 後ろだ!!
ぐあっ！ 目が…。
My eye...!
カカシ！
Kakashi!
おい カカシ！ 大丈夫か!?
Hey Kakashi! Are you all right?!
(タイセキ)たとえ ガキ相手とはいえ
用心に こしたこたぁねぇ。
Even if he's just a kid,
it doesn't hurt to be cautious...
じっくりいくか。
I'll take it nice and slow.
敵のヤツ… やり手だよ。
Our enemy... He's good...
オレの血の匂いのついたクナイは
ちゃんと 捨ててやがる。
He threw away the kunai knife stained
with the smell of my blood.
また 目にゴミでも入ったのかよ。
Don't tell me you got dust
in your eye again?
忍が 泣くなっての。
A ninja shouldn't cry...
まだ 死んだわけじゃない。
気を抜くなよ。
I'm not dead yet.
Stay focused!
((ゴーグルしてるのに
目に ゴミが入るわけないよね。
There's no way dust can
get into your eyes
when you have goggles on.
自制心を口にするなら➡
If you're going to advocate self-control,
don't just mouth the words.
(口だけじゃなく
心も強くもたないと))
Act strong too.
《オレは いつも口先だけで➡
I'm just talk...
Always being saved by others...
みんなに
助けられてばっかだ。
口先だけの落ちこぼれだ。
けど…》
Just a big-mouthed loser...
But...
((オレは 白い牙を
本当の英雄だと思ってる。
I believe that the White Fang
was a true hero...
(仲間を大切にしないヤツは
それ以上のクズだ))
Those who abandon their comrades...
are worse than scum!
《あの言葉だけは 口先だけに
したくはないんだ！》
I don't want those words
to be just empty talk!
(タイセキ)死ね!!
Die!
(タイセキ)な… なぜだ。
見えるわけはない。
Wh-Why...?
There's no way you can see...
オビト… お前！
Obito... You...!
な… なんだ。 その目は…。
Wh-What is... that eye...?
ここは…
仲間はオレが守る！
This time... I'll protect my comrade!
オビト… お前その目！
Obito... That eye of yours...
ああ… これが写輪眼みてえだ。
Yeah... I guess this is the Sharingan.
チャクラの動きや流れが
目に見える。
I can now see the movement
and flow of chakra.
大丈夫か カカシ！
Are you all right, Kakashi?!
Yeah...
ああ… どうやら左目は
もう ダメそうだが➡
Looks like I lost my left eye,
リンからもらった これがある。
but I have the kit Rin gave me.
応急処置なら すぐできる。
I can use it for emergency first-aid.
すぐに リンを助けに行くぞ！
おう！
We're going to save Rin immediately!
Okay!
You're surprisingly stubborn.
意外に しぶといヤツだ。
Hmm.... They're all so pathetic.
どいつもコイツも だらしねえ。
リンの チャクラの流れが荒れてる！
The flow of Rin's chakra is disturbed...
オレや お前の
チャクラの動きと違うぞ！
It's different from your chakra
or mine.
おそらく 幻術に かけられてる…。
She's probably under a genjutsu...
すぐにでも
情報を 聞き出そうとしたんだ。
They didn't waste any time trying
to get the information out of her.
フン… どうやら
ただのガキどもじゃないようだな。
It seems they're not mere kids.
一度 手合わせしたが
かなりの早技だ！
We fought him earlier.
He's fast... Stay alert!
気をつけろ！
おう！
Right!
解！
Release!
カカシ… オビト…。
Kakashi... Obito...!
助けにきたぞ リン！
もう 大丈夫だ！
We've come to save you, Rin!
You'll be all right now.
よし！ あとは さっさと退散だ！
All right, now let's get out of here!
なるほど…
いいコンビネーションだったが➡
I see...
You two made a good team,
but you're still just kids.
しょせん ガキだな。
今 お前らのいるのは
敵の 手のなかだぜ。
Right now, you're in enemy hands.
Earth Style: Rock Breaker!
土遁！ 岩宿崩し!!
やばい！
This is bad!!
出口に走れ!!
Run for the exit!
ぐわっ！
カカシ!!
Kakashi!
Too bad, I lost a good source
of information...
せっかくの情報源だったが…➡
Oh well, it can't be helped.
まぁ しかたねえか。
くっ…。
大丈夫か？ リン… カカシ…。
Are you all right?
Rin...? Kakashi...?
(カカシ)オビト!!
Obito!
ううっ…！ くっ…!!
やめろ…。
Don't... It's okay, Kakashi.
いいんだ カカシ…。
オレは… もう ダメみたいだ…。
I don't think...I can make it...
体の右側は
ほとんど潰れちまって…➡
My right side is totally crushed.
I can't even feel anything...
感覚すら… ねえ…。
くっ！ ハァ ハァ…。
クソ～ッ！
Dammit!!
いや… そんな… どうして…。
No... This can't be... Why...?
オビト!!
Obito...!
Dammit!
チクショウ！ チクショウ!!
Dammit!!
If...If only I had listened to you,
オレが… オレが 初めから
お前の言うとおりに➡
一緒に リンを助けにきてたら➡
and we had come to rescue Rin
in the first place...
こんなことには
ならなかったんだ～!!
This never would've happened!
なにが 隊長だ… なにが 上忍だ!!
So what if I'm a captain?!
So what if I made jonin?!
Oh yeah... I had forgotten...
そういや… 忘れてたぜ…。
オレだけ…➡
I was the only one who...
didn't give you a gift...
お前に 上忍祝いのプレゼント…➡
for becoming a jonin, Kakashi.
やってなかったな… カカシ…。
何が いいか… 考えてたんだ…。
I was...wondering what to give you...
and I just had a thought.
んでよ… 今… 思いついたんだ…。
なに… 安心しろ…。
Don't worry...
It's not some useless, extra baggage...
役に立たない…➡
よけいな… もんじゃない…。
この オレの写輪眼をやるからよ。
I'm giving you...my Sharingan.
里のヤツらが何て言おうと➡
Whatever the village may say...
you are...a great jonin.
お前は立派な上忍だ。
That's how I really feel...
それがオレの気持だ。
So please accept it.
受け取ってくれ。
リン お前の医療忍術で➡
Rin... Use your Medical Ninjutsu...
Take the entire eye and transplant...
my Sharingan...
オレの写輪眼を眼軸ごと➡
into Kakashi's left eye.
カカシの左目に移殖してくれ。
Kakashi, come over here...
I'll start it right away.
カカシ こっちに来て。
すぐ始めるから。
オレは もう死ぬ。
I'm about to...die...
But...I'll become your eye and...
けど お前の目になって➡
see the future...for you.
これから先を見てやるからよ。
How stubborn...
You're still alive, huh?
しぶてえな…
まだ生きてやがったか。
が… やっぱりガキだな。
But...you're just a kid, after all.
What's a ninja crying for?
忍が何泣いてやがる。
Come on, crybaby! Let's settle this.
来な 泣き虫。 ケリつけてやるぜ。
That kid...
He seems different than before...
《あのガキ
さっきと様子が少し違うな》
カカシ リンを頼むぜ。
Kakashi...take care of...Rin.
あぁ。
Yeah...
Don't panic...Rin.
慌てるなよ リン。
ハァ ハァ…。
Kakashi... Take Rin...
カカシ リンを… リンを連れて早く➡
Take Rin and...get out...of here.
ここを離れろ。
Enemy reinforcements...
will be coming.
敵の援軍が来るぞ。
Obito...
オビト…。
いいから行け。
It's okay... Just go...
リン！
Rin!
Earth Style! Earthquake Slam!
土遁！ 裂土転掌！
リン 早くつかまれ！
リン！
Rin, hurry, take my hand!
Rin!
オビト！
Obito!!
《カカシのヤツと➡
Just when Kakashi and I were...
starting to get along...
せっかく仲よくなれたのに➡
リンには結局➡
I couldn't tell Rin that I...
loved her...
告白できなかったなぁ…。
みんなと➡
I wish...I could've spent more time...
with everyone.
もっと一緒にいたかった…》
オビト！
Obito!
Damn it...!
チクショウ！
オビト
お前が完成させてくれた術だ。
Obito... This is the jutsu
you helped me perfect!
ほうほう こんな状況で
まだ闘う意志を見せるとは➡
Hmm... You still have the will to fight,
even in this situation?
敵地後方まで
コソコソ潜り込んでくるだけはあるな。
No wonder you were able to sneak
so deep into enemy territory.
気が強い。
You are a determined one.
リン！ コイツらはオレが足止めする。
Rin! I'll hold them off!
Get out now!
その隙に逃げろ！
でも…！
But...!
オレはオビトに お前を頼まれたんだ。
I promised Obito I'd look after you...
だから お前は死んでも守る！
I'll protect you with my life!
カカシ…。
Kakashi...
リン オビトはお前のことが
好きだったんだ。
Rin... Obito cared about you.
大好きだった 大切だった。
He loved you...
You were everything to him.
That's why he gave his life
to protect you.
だから 命がけで守ろうとした。
Then, Kakashi! You should know
my feelings for you...
なら カカシ！ 私の気持だって…!!
I...!
オレは！
I tried to abandon you...
オレは一度
お前を見捨てようとしたクズだ。
I'm nothing but scum.
Rin, go!
行け！ リン!!
オレは… 死んだのか？
Am I...dead?
ここは？
Where am I?
気がついたみたいだね。
Looks like
you've regained consciousness.
Huh?!
先生！ どうして？
Sensei! But how...?
このクナイの術式は
オレが時空間忍術で➡
The jutsu formula on this kunai knife
serves as a marker
飛び回るための目印なんだよ。
when I leap using
the Transportation Technique.
じゃあ 敵は？
Then...the enemy?
I took them all down...
オレが全員 倒したよ。
リンは？ リンはどこなんです!?
Rin...
Where is Rin?!
I'm sorry
I couldn't make it in time, Kakashi...
間に合わなくて
すまなかった カカシ。
話は全部 リンから聞いたよ。
Rin told me everything.
The Third Great Ninja War.
＜第三次忍界大戦
その長きにわたる戦いは➡
With the sacrifice of
many nameless ninja,
this long war finally came to a close.
名も無き多くの
忍たちの犠牲によって終結した。
In its wake, it also left legends...
そして 同時に名だたる英雄たち➡
The stories of great heroes,
語り継がれる伝説を
残したのである。
to be told and retold
for generations to come.
神無毘橋の戦い。
The Battle of Kannabi Bridge...
That day, two heroes were born
in the Hidden Leaf Village,
その日 木ノ葉隠れに➡
each with his own Sharingan.
２人の写輪眼を持つ
英雄が生まれた。
１人は その名を慰霊碑に刻み➡
One found his name engraved
on the memorial stone.
The other came to be known
as "Kakashi of the Sharingan."
１人は のちに
写輪眼のカカシと呼ばれ➡
In time, the tales of his bravery spanned
all borders, and beyond.
他国にまで
その勇名を轟かせるのである＞
Capture Itachi Uchiha...
(パンサーリリー)
『FAIRY TAIL』 前回までは…。
(メスト)知りたい…
あらすじというものを➡
It won't be an easy mission.
俺は知りたい。
(パンサーリリー)怪しすぎる。
But it's something I can't avoid.
(シャルル)てなわけで
Ｓ級試験に参加中のメストが➡
ギルドの者じゃないかもしれない
と思った私たちは➡
To bring back Sasuke, eh?
天狼島に向かったってわけ。
I'm sure you're aware of this,
(パンサーリリー)怪しすぎる。
but Sasuke is now powerful enough
to even kill Orochimaru.
(シャルル)そして島には
もっと大変な危機が➡
I know that.
But I never
迫りつつあったの。
(メスト)知りたい。
危機というものを 俺は…。
(パンサーリリー)
だから 怪しすぎるだろ！